<item id="129" name="networking" parent="128" title="Networking" zoneName="" templateKey="Index" state="16" created="09/22/2013 19:41:04" updated="04/12/2014 06:13:51" published="09/22/2013 19:34:06" expires="" sortOrder="-10" url="/ContentPages/Index?n2page=129" visible="True" savedBy="admin" typeName="Dinamico.Models.ContentPage, ElixTech.V3" discriminator="ContentPage" versionIndex="1" ancestralTrail="/1/4/111/128/" alteredPermissions="0" childState="2"><details><detail name="Author" typeName="System.String, mscorlib" meta="" /><detail name="Keywords" typeName="System.String, mscorlib" meta="" /><detail name="Description" typeName="System.String, mscorlib" meta="" /><detail name="SeoTitle" typeName="System.String, mscorlib" meta="" /><detail name="Text" typeName="System.String, mscorlib" meta="" encoded="True"><![CDATA[&lt;h2&gt;Home Networks&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you are a family that simply needs an internet connection on all computers, or you need enhanced functionality with&amp;nbsp;the ability to share files, folders, and printers, you need a home network. We specialize in setting up in-home wired and wireless networks that are lightning-fast and secure. Optionally deploy a second network for your guests, so they can enjoy wireless access to the web without compromising the security or performance of your own PCs. Connect your mobile devices to your in-home WiFi to save on data charges while you&amp;#39;re at home. Enable secure remote access to your computers from any other internet-connected PC in the world. The possibilities are limitless!&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Home networks start at just $399&amp;nbsp;with all hardware included! Services are available in the Morristown, NJ area, Seattle, WA area, and the San Francisco Bay area/San Jose, CA.&amp;nbsp;Please contact us today for more information.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Corporate Networks&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Domain controllers are more suitable for situations when large numbers of users need to access a network. We would typically install&amp;nbsp;domain controller or server (if needed), a router - wired, wireless, or both - and configure all computers in your organization appropriately.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A corporate network allows your business to&amp;nbsp;connect all of the computers in your business and&amp;nbsp;home offices securely. This helps to prevent against unauthorized access to your network. You can classify users into different groups&amp;nbsp;and designate different permissions and policies that define what users are able to do. You can restrict access to the domain, computers, printers, and files from potentially harmful or inexperienced users. For example, at a school,&amp;nbsp;the &amp;quot;teachers&amp;quot; group has more access to programs and Windows components than the &amp;quot;students&amp;quot; group has. This prevents the children from accidentally harming the system, installing programs, or accessing unauthorized files and folders.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Services are available in the Morristown, NJ area, Seattle, WA area, and the San Francisco Bay area/San Jose, CA.&amp;nbsp;Please contact us today for more information and a no-obligation cost proposal.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
]]></detail></details><detailCollections /><children /><authorizations /><properties><property name="Summary" typeName="System.String, mscorlib"><![CDATA[]]></property><property name="Image" typeName="System.String, mscorlib"><![CDATA[]]></property></properties></item>