<item id="132" name="pc-maintenance" parent="129" title="PC Maintenance" zoneName="" templateKey="Index" state="16" created="09/22/2013 18:46:37" updated="05/09/2014 22:34:36" published="09/22/2013 18:46:22" expires="" sortOrder="-2" url="/ContentPages/Index?n2page=132" visible="True" savedBy="admin" typeName="Dinamico.Models.ContentPage, ElixTech.V3" discriminator="ContentPage" versionIndex="2" ancestralTrail="/2/5/112/129/" alteredPermissions="0" childState="2"><details><detail name="Author" typeName="System.String, mscorlib" meta="" /><detail name="Keywords" typeName="System.String, mscorlib" meta="" /><detail name="Description" typeName="System.String, mscorlib" meta="" /><detail name="SeoTitle" typeName="System.String, mscorlib" meta="" /><detail name="Text" typeName="System.String, mscorlib" meta="" encoded="True"><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;Keep your business PCs running at top performance with a maintenance solution from Elix Technologies. We will ensure that your business PCs and servers are always running the latest security updates and software. In addition, we can help your company ensure that you remain compliant with software licensing requirements.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Computer Running Slow?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Hard Drives&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Install a&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;solid-state drive&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;for peak performance. Many of our customers report speed-ups of 2x to 10x prior performance, and&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;boot-up times reduced to as little as 7 seconds&lt;/strong&gt;. In many cases, we can perform the upgrade in-place without compromising any data.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Running low on storage? Install one or more&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;additional hard drives&lt;/strong&gt;, available in a variety of sizes to meet all your storage needs. We can also upgrade storage in-place, without compromising any data, in case there isn&amp;#39;t room for another drive -- ideal for laptops!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Memory&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Run more programs at once and cache data for faster access. Memory is an inexpensive upgrade that can boost the performance of your computer dramatically.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Graphics Card/GPU&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Installing a new graphics card boosts the performance of graphical applications including CAD software, 3D rendering software, Microsoft Office, web browsing, and video games.&lt;/p&gt;
]]></detail></details><detailCollections /><children /><authorizations /><properties><property name="Summary" typeName="System.String, mscorlib"><![CDATA[]]></property><property name="Image" typeName="System.String, mscorlib"><![CDATA[]]></property></properties></item>