<item id="7" name="organizing-photos" parent="6" title="Organizing Photos" zoneName="" templateKey="Index" state="16" created="09/22/2013 19:05:27" updated="04/12/2014 06:13:08" published="09/22/2013 19:05:22" expires="" sortOrder="0" url="/ContentPages/Index?n2page=7" visible="True" savedBy="admin" typeName="Dinamico.Models.ContentPage, ElixTech.V3" discriminator="ContentPage" versionIndex="3" ancestralTrail="/1/4/5/6/" alteredPermissions="0" childState="2"><details><detail name="Author" typeName="System.String, mscorlib" meta="" /><detail name="Keywords" typeName="System.String, mscorlib" meta="" /><detail name="Description" typeName="System.String, mscorlib" meta="" /><detail name="SeoTitle" typeName="System.String, mscorlib" meta="" /><detail name="Text" typeName="System.String, mscorlib" meta="" encoded="True"><![CDATA[&lt;h2&gt;1. Photo Staging&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First, someone has taken photos with their digital camera. When the memory card is full (or as needed), the photos are downloaded to the computer and loaded into that user&amp;#39;s&amp;nbsp;&lt;em&gt;Photo Staging&lt;/em&gt;&amp;nbsp;folder on SkyDrive, where they are uploaded. Some editing can take place here; bad and unncessary photos can and should be deleted as appropriate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;2. Lightroom Catalog and Processing&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At that point, the photos are downloaded into a centralized Adobe Lightroom catalog. For extra reliability, the Lightroom catalog is stored on a volume with redundancy&amp;nbsp;functionality provided by Windows 8 Storage Spaces. It&amp;#39;s also backed up regularly to an external hard drive and synchronized using Bittorrent Sync to an offsite location for extra reliability.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Photos may be further edited and de-duplicated in Lightroom.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;3. Photo &amp;amp;&amp;nbsp;Video&amp;nbsp;Export&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Photos are exported in Lightroom into one location with a path that corresponds roughly to the following:&amp;nbsp;&lt;em&gt;E:\Photos\Family Photos\{Year}\{Year}-{Month}&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;and an optional day and event. For example,&amp;nbsp;&lt;em&gt;E:\Photos\Family Photos\2013\2013-05 Bethany&amp;#39;s Graduation&lt;/em&gt;. The photos are exported as high-quality JPEG images. The high-quality family photos directory is published via Bittorrent Sync secret, and anyone who wishes to have a copy of the high-quality JPEGs on his or her machine may sync this set of files.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Video files are copied to this location as well and transcoded to H.264 if necessary, since the Motion JPEG codec that many digital cameras use is not space efficient. I use Vidcoder, a free program, to accomplish this (&lt;a href=&quot;http://vidcoder.codeplex.com/&quot;&gt;http://vidcoder.codeplex.com/&lt;/a&gt;).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;4. Photo &amp;amp;&amp;nbsp;Video Publishing&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For mobile consumption and circumstances where someone may not want the full 80+ GB of hi-res family photos, I have written a tool called PhotoPublish (&lt;a href=&quot;https://bitbucket.org/bherila/photopublish&quot;&gt;https://bitbucket.org/bherila/photopublish&lt;/a&gt;)&amp;nbsp;which copies and converts JPEG images in the hi-resolution output discussed in Step 3 to a lower-resolution version (typically 1920 pixels on the long edge, but with a target file size of ~400 KB) suitable for sharing. The lower-resolution photos are uploaded to SkyDrive. These photos are never synced to other PCs but are always available for online viewing.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Currently, my SkyDrive photo collection contains 43,553 files consuming 7.29 GB of space. So you can see how even the free 7 GB SkyDrive plan can get you quite far with your photo sharing!&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;5. Photo Printing Services&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Print services don&amp;#39;t have a convenient sync mechanism so I typically just upload photos ad-hoc, as I want to print them.&lt;/p&gt;
]]></detail></details><detailCollections><collection name="TrackedLinks"><detail name="TrackedLinks" typeName="N2.Details.IMultipleValue, N2" meta="Text"><value key="Bool">True</value><value key="Int">1746</value><value key="Link">0</value><value key="String" encoded="True"><![CDATA[http://vidcoder.codeplex.com/]]></value></detail><detail name="TrackedLinks" typeName="N2.Details.IMultipleValue, N2" meta="Text"><value key="Bool">True</value><value key="Int">2033</value><value key="Link">0</value><value key="String" encoded="True"><![CDATA[https://bitbucket.org/bherila/photopublish]]></value></detail></collection></detailCollections><children /><authorizations /><properties><property name="Summary" typeName="System.String, mscorlib"><![CDATA[]]></property><property name="Image" typeName="System.String, mscorlib"><![CDATA[]]></property></properties></item>