<item id="9" name="" parent="8" title="" zoneName="Left" templateKey="Index" state="16" created="10/07/2012 02:16:00" updated="04/12/2014 06:13:08" published="10/07/2012 02:16:00" expires="" sortOrder="0" url="/StartPage/Index?n2page=5&amp;n2item=9" visible="True" savedBy="admin" typeName="Dinamico.Models.ContentPart, ElixTech.V3" discriminator="ContentPart" versionIndex="0" ancestralTrail="/1/4/5/8/" alteredPermissions="0" childState="2"><details><detail name="Text" typeName="System.String, mscorlib" meta="" encoded="True"><![CDATA[&lt;h1&gt;Welcome&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Welcome to my&amp;nbsp;&lt;span&gt;blog&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp;home page. I&#39;m currently working on filling it with content, but in the meantime please feel free to browse around :-)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;This is not a blog.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I really don&#39;t like the notion of blogging. Yet here I am. This site is not meant to be an online catalogue of my every waking moment and observation. It&#39;s really just a collection of information that will hopefully be useful to you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Purpose?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This site serves three main purposes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;First&lt;/strong&gt;, to remain connected with friends and family. Although I post some content on Facebook, Google+, Flickr, and other social media sites, I like to stay in control of my information. Furthermore, none of these sites allow me to effectively manage&amp;nbsp;&lt;em&gt;all&lt;/em&gt;&amp;nbsp;of my shareable content. I&#39;ll stick the balance here. (Much of this content is invisible unless you are&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&quot;http://bherila.net/Login.aspx&quot;&gt;logged in&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Second&lt;/strong&gt;, to share things that are worth sharing. What&#39;s worth sharing, you ask? I believe that if it has the possibility to make someone&#39;s life better, it&#39;s worth sharing. And that&#39;s why you can find all sorts of things like my favorite recipes that I&#39;ve collected and concocted over the past 22 years of my life :-)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Third&lt;/strong&gt;, to serve as an online resume, a digital business card, etc. You know what I mean. I can&#39;t just sit around doing nothing all day, and maintaining all these expensive hobbies means I need to stay competitive in the job market.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Who I am&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&#39;m a recent graduate of Brown University who is now a&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;Program Manager&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;at a large software company. I design and build websites and software applications that don&#39;t compete with my employer in my spare time, and also enjoy cooking, skiing, and singing classical choral music as a tenor.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Last but not least&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thanks for visiting! If you have any questions please feel free to&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&quot;http://bherila.net/Contact.aspx&quot;&gt;contact me&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;- you can use the contact page or, if I&#39;m online, the IM widget floating at the bottom of your browser.&lt;/p&gt;]]></detail><detail name="VersionKey" typeName="System.String, mscorlib" meta="" encoded="True"><![CDATA[89c7c4ea-b228-4b21-8c11-58bb4f05c2d1]]></detail></details><detailCollections><collection name="TrackedLinks"><detail name="TrackedLinks" typeName="N2.Details.IMultipleValue, N2" meta="Text"><value key="Bool">True</value><value key="Int">935</value><value key="Link">0</value><value key="String" encoded="True"><![CDATA[http://bherila.net/Login.aspx]]></value></detail><detail name="TrackedLinks" typeName="N2.Details.IMultipleValue, N2" meta="Text"><value key="Bool">True</value><value key="Int">2038</value><value key="Link">0</value><value key="String" encoded="True"><![CDATA[http://bherila.net/Contact.aspx]]></value></detail></collection></detailCollections><children /><authorizations /><properties /></item>